I JUST WALKED
IN THE BATHROOM
AND SAW KATHY NAKED.
IT WAS LIKE TORTURE.
YOU KNOW, IF WE EVER GO
TO WAR AND YOU'RE CAPTURED
YOU'RE IN FOR A BIG SURPRISE.
IT JUST KEEPS
GETTING WORSE.
IT'S BAD ENOUGH THAT
I'M IN LOVE WITH MY
ROOMMATE'S GIRLFRIEND
WHICH I THINK
SHE KNOWS.
EVERY TIME WE'RE
IN THE SAME ROOM TOGETHER
THERE'S THIS WEIRD ENERGY
BETWEEN US.
AND CALL ME CRAZY
BUT I THINK
SHE LIKES ME, TOO.
AND NOW...
I HAVE SEEN HER NAKED.
AT LEAST, WHEN I'D SEEN HER
WITH CLOTHES ON
I COULD IMAGINE THAT HER BODY
WAS COVERED IN BOILS
OR SOMETHING.
BUT THERE ARE NO BOILS.
SHE'S SMOOTH.
SMOOTH!
WOW.
COULD EVERYONE SEE UP HIS ROBE?
YEAH, RIGHT
UP IT.
OH, MY GOD!
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
GREAT. ALL RIGHT.
SO I'LL
CALL YOU LATER.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
WHO WAS THAT?
THAT WOULD BE CACEY.
WE'RE GOING OUT TONIGHT.
GOING OUT, HUH?
WOW! WOW!
SO, THINGS DIDN'T WORK
OUT WITH KATHY, HUH?
BUMMER.
NO, THINGS ARE FINE
WITH KATHY.
I'M HAVING A LATE DINNER
WITH HER TONIGHT
RIGHT AFTER
MY EARLY DINNER
WITH CACEY.
WHAT?
AND THE CRAZIEST THING IS
I JUST ATE A WHOLE PIZZA
MYSELF.
BUT...
YOU'RE GOING OUT
WITH KATHY.
YEAH.
WHY ARE YOU UPSET?
WELL, I'M UPSET...
FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN
HAVING SEX WITH AN ENDLESS LINE
OF BEAUTIFUL WOMEN
MUST BE VERY UNFULFILLING
FOR YOU.
WHAT IS THE BIG DEAL?
IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'RE EXCLUSIVE.
LOOK, JOEY
KATHY IS CLEARLY NOT FULFILLING
YOUR EMOTIONAL NEEDS
BUT CACEY...
I MEAN, GRANTED, I JUST SAW
THE BACK OF HER HEAD
BUT I GOT THIS SENSE
THAT SHE'S SMART
AND FUNNY AND GETS YOU.
YOU GOT ALL THAT FROM
THE BACK OF HER HEAD?
I JUST THINK IT'S TIME
FOR YOU TO SETTLE DOWN--
YOU KNOW, MAKE A CHOICE,
PICK A LANE.
WHO'S ELAINE?
♪ LITTLE TINY TARZAN ♪
♪ SWINGING ON A NOSE HAIR ♪
♪ SWINGING WITH THE
GREATEST OF EASE... ♪
( clears throat, hums melody)
DARN IT. I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO GET TO THE NEXT VERSE.
YOU COULD JUST GO, UH...
♪ GREATEST OF EASE ♪
♪ BUM-A-NUMMA-NUMMA... ♪
AND THEN GO RIGHT INTO IT.
YEAH.
OOH, I LIKE THAT.
WAIT. HOW DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT "BUM-A-NUMMA-NUMMAS"?
WELL, UH...
YOU KNOW, I USED TO PLAY.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THE KEYBOARDS, HUH?
YEAH. JUST A LITTLE
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
I REALLY GOT INTO
IT IN COLLEGE.
THAT'S WHEN I REALLY
FOUND MY SOUND.
( chokes, laughs )
OH, GOD. ORANGE JUICE
JUST CAME OUT OF MY NOSE
BUT IT WAS
TOTALLY WORTH IT.
OH, MY GOD!
I COMPLETELY FORGOT
ABOUT YOUR SOUND.
YEAH.
HE USED TO LOCK HIMSELF
IN THE BASEMENT FOR HOURS.
NO ONE WAS EVER ALLOWED
TO HEAR "THE SOUND."
I WANT TO HEAR "THE SOUND."
NO. I MEAN...
NO, I HAVEN'T PLAYED IN SO LONG
AND, AND...
WELL, IT'S REALLY
PERSONAL STUFF, YOU KNOW?
COME ON. PLAY THAT FUNKY MUSIC,
WHITE BOY.
YEAH, COME ON.
NO, YOU GUYS.
MY KEYBOARDS ARE ALL THE WAY...
YEAH, OKAY.
OKAY, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, BRING
IT ON, YOU.
( clears throat )
HERE WE GO.
( inhales )
( single note )
YOU KNOW,
I'VE NEVER PLAYED MY STUFF
FOR ANYONE BEFORE
SO IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT YOU UNDERSTAND
IT'S ABOUT COMMUNICATING...
VERY PRIVATE EMOTIONS.
YOU KNOW, UM...
YOU SHOULD THINK OF, UM...
MY WORK
AS WORDLESS SOUND POEMS.
THAT'S WHAT...
OH, MY GOD. PLAY!
( boogie woogie accompaniment)
( dog barking )
( cow mooing )
( rooster crows, dog barks )
( buzzing )
( doorbell ringing )
( laser zapping )
( rattling )
( explosion )
BOY, YOU KNOW,
TH-THAT WAS, UH...
TERRIFIC.
REALLY...
BITCHIN'.
WOW!
IT WAS SO... WOW!
REALLY? I MEAN, REALLY?
OH, YEAH!
I MEAN, YOU SHOULD...
PLAY IN PUBLIC.
WOW! THANKS, YOU GUYS!
THAT'S, OH...
OH, I WANT TO PLAY YOU
ANOTHER PIECE.
UM... OH!
I LEFT MY HELICOPTER SOUNDS
ON ANOTHER DISK.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, OKAY?
OH, THIS IS...
THIS IS SO NICE.
I MEAN, I AM SO...
OH, GOD BLESS MY DAD
FOR SOUNDPROOFING THE BASEMENT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I EVER LET HIM
TOUCH ME WITH THOSE FINGERS.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I LOVED IT!
IT WAS SO MOVING.
PLUS, IT'S SO DIFFERENT
FROM THE STUFF
YOU USUALLY HEAR.
YOU MEAN MUSIC?
( quacking )
YEAH, I KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
YES, YES. YOUR BREASTS
ARE JUST AS FIRM AND JUICY.
( knocking )
COME IN.
HEY.
OH, GOD. IS THAT BAYWATCH?
UH, YES, BUT, UH, I JUST
WATCH IT FOR THE ARTICLES.
SO, IS JOEY AROUND?
NO. HE'S NOT BACK YET, BUT HE'S
GOING TO BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
HAVE A SEAT. BOW OR STERN?
I DON'T REALLY HAVE
A PREFERENCE. YOU?
WELL, I LIKE IT IN THE STERN.
OF THE BOAT.
( phone rings )
HELLO.
HEY, IT'S ME.
LISTEN, CACEY AND I HAD
A LITTLE CAR TROUBLE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
We broke down
ON THE PARKWAY.
I HAVE TO GET
SOME TRANSMISSION FLUID.
COULD YOU PLEASE TELL KATHY I'M
SORRY AND I'LL BE THERE SOON?
WHY CAN'T YOU TELL HER?
'Cause I only have one quarter
and my time is about to...
JOEY? JOEY?
YEAH?
I THOUGHT YOUR TIME RAN OUT.
ME, TOO, BUT I GUESS
I DO HAVE A COUPLE OF...
UH, THAT WAS JOEY.
HE'S RUNNING A LITTLE LATE
AND HE SAYS HE'S SORRY.
SO I GUESS IT'S JUST
YOU AND ME, THEN.
OH. OKAY.
YEAH. I THINK IT IS.
SO, WHAT DID YOU DO TODAY?
I HAD AN APPOINTMENT
TO GET MY HAIR CUT...
IT LOOKS GREAT.
AND THEN IT GOT CANCELED.
WELL, I COULD CUT IT.
REALLY? DO YOU DO THAT?
YEAH, I DO.
I LEARNED IT IN MY AUNT'S
DOG-GROOMING SHOP
BUT WHAT DO YOU SAY?
DOG-GROOMING, HUH?
OKAY, JUST DON'T MAKE
MY TAIL TOO POOFY.
YOU HAVE
REALLY GREAT HAIR.
WELL, THANKS.
I GROW IT MYSELF.
MMM!
MMM...
YOU KNOW WHO ALSO
HAS GREAT HAIR IS JOEY.
YES. YEAH, JOEY
HAS GREAT HAIR.
UM, I'M BASICALLY
DONE HERE.
LET ME JUST GET
THIS HAIR OFF YOUR NECK.
WH-WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
CHECKING TO SEE
IF IT'S EVEN.
'KAY.
IT LOOKS GOOD.
( phone ringing )
IT'S THE PHONE!
THE PHONE'S MAKING SOUNDS!
HELLO.
HEY, DUDE, IT'S ME.
HEY, IT'S JOEY.
OH.
WE'RE GOING TO BE STUCK HERE
FOR A WHILE.
I GOT THE TRANSMISSION FLUID,
WENT TO PUT IT IN THE CAR--
THE TRANSMISSION WASN'T THERE.
WHAT?
It must've fallen out
A FEW BLOCKS BACK.
I FIGURED WE HIT A DOG.
OH. OKAY.
Could you put Kathy on?
I want to apologize to her.
OH. YEAH, MAN. JOEY.
HEY.
OH, NO. IT'S FINE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
NO, STOP APOLOGIZING.
IT'S OKAY.
YEAH. I'LL TALK
TO YOU TOMORROW.
I SHOULD, UH,
PROBABLY GO.
YEAH. YES. YEAH.
( knock at door )
I FORGOT MY PURSE.
OH.
OH! I REALLY DID.
I FORGOT MY PURSE.
( mumbling
incoherently )
OH, NO!
THIS IS BAD, IT'S BAD.
THIS IS BAD.
HORRIBLE.
WAIT, THE, UH, THE KISS,
OR THE SITUATION?
NO, THE KISS WAS GOOD.
NO, BUT THAT'S BAD!
OH, YES!
OKAY, HERE'S WHAT WE DO.
WE FORGET IT HAPPENED.
WHAT?
WE SWALLOW OUR FEELINGS
EVEN IF IT MEANS
WE'RE UNHAPPY FOREVER.
SOUND GOOD?
CAN YOU REALLY DO THAT?
I HAVE TO.
HE'S MY BEST FRIEND...
AND YOU'RE SEEING HIM.
OH, CHANDLER, I LIKE JOEY A LOT
BUT WITH YOU...
OH, NO, NO, DON'T. SEE?
SEE, YOU'RE GETTING ME CONFUSED.
I'M STARTING TO YEARN.
I'M SORRY.
IF YOU WANT TO PRETEND
THAT NOTHING HAPPENED
I CAN TRY.
I-I THINK WE HAVE TO.
OKAY.
BYE.
( door opens and shuts )
ARE YOU STILL OUT THERE?
NO.
( shrill, abrasive
synthesizer melodies )
( distorted):
ELECTRIFYING...
INFINITE TIME...
( echoing ):
TIME... TIME... TIME...
YOU KNOW, THERE'S
A STARBUCKS ABOUT
THREE BLOCKS DOWN.
HE'S SO INSPIRED.
JUST LOOK AT HIM.
LOOK AT HIM GO.
( spacy noodling )
( clock ticking )
( explosion )
( polite applause )
( distorted echo ):
THANK YOU, NEW YORK...
NEW YORK... NEW YORK...
HEY, AREN'T
YOU UP NEXT?
OH, NO.
I'M NOT PLAYING TONIGHT.
WHY NOT?
I CAN'T FOLLOW ROSS.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THAT WOULD BE LIKE THOSE
POOR BICYCLE-RIDING CHIMPS
WHO HAD TO FOLLOW
THE BEATLES. NO.
PHOEBE, ROSS SUCKS.
PHOEBE,
THE PLACE HAS EMPTIED
BECAUSE OF HIM.
OH, MY GOD,
HE'S NOT EVEN APPRECIATED
IN HIS OWN TIME.
I WOULD GIVE ANYTHING
TO NOT BE APPRECIATED
IN MY OWN TIME!
OKAY. UM, PHOEBE...
YOU SUCK, TOO.
YEAH, PHOEBE, YOU'RE...
AWFUL!
YOU GUYS.
"YEAH, YOU SUCK, TOO."
OH, MAN!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I LOCKED MYSELF OUT AGAIN!
HANG ON, BUDDY.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
DID YOU DO ALL THIS?
I SURE DID.
WHY?
I JUST THOUGHT
IT WOULD MAKE ME FEEL GOOD
TO DO SOMETHING NICE
FOR MY FRIEND.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS AMAZING.
A TV THAT APPEARS
AS IF FROM NOWHERE!
THAT'S THE DREAM!
HOW DID YOU
AFFORD ALL THIS STUFF?!
WELL, YOU KNOW, I'M 29.
I MEAN,
WHO NEEDS A SAVINGS ACCOUNT?
YOU ARE THE BEST FRIEND
ANYONE HAS EVER HAD.
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
NO, NO, NO, YOU ARE.
YOU DO THIS, YOU GIVE
ME THE GREAT ADVICE
AND LISTEN, I WAS
THINKING ABOUT WHAT
YOU SAID YESTERDAY
ABOUT FOCUSING
ON ONE WOMAN?
I'M GOING TO DO THAT.
YOU MEAN WITH CACEY?
NO. I THINK I'LL SEE
HOW THINGS GO WITH KATHY.
SHE'S PRETTY COOL.
OR CACEY.
NO, NO, KATHY.
COULD BE CACEY.
CONSIDER CACEY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
I THINK SOMEBODY'S
GOT A LITTLE
CRUSH ON CACEY.
HOW ABOUT I
FIX YOU TWO UP?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THAT ALL THE PIECES
OF MY LIFE
ARE FALLING
RIGHT INTO PLACE.
HEY.
HEY, YOU WERE
REALLY GREAT.
YOU WERE REALLY,
THANKS.
SO, MONICA TELLS ME
THAT, UH, YOU DON'T
WANT TO PLAY ANYMORE
BECAUSE OF ME
AND, YOU KNOW,
MY TALENT.
IS THAT TRUE?
WELL...
KIND OF, YEAH. YEAH.
PHEEBS...
YEAH, I MEAN, YOU KNOW
AND I WAS TRYING TO BE
REALLY, YOU KNOW, OKAY
AND UPBEAT ABOUT IT
BUT I FEEL SO...
DWARFED BY YOUR MUSICAL GIFT.
I...
SEE, BUT PHEEBS
THAT IS THE EXACT
OPPOSITE INTENT
OF MY MUSIC.
MY MUSIC IS MEANT
TO INSPIRE
AND IF IT BOTHERS
YOU THIS MUCH
THEN I...
I WON'T PLAY ANYMORE.
OH, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
DON'T DO THAT.
HOW COULD I LIVE
WITH MYSELF
IF I KNEW I WAS DEPRIVING
THE WORLD OF YOUR MUSIC?
YEAH, OKAY.
SAW THE NEW
FURNITURE.
VERY NICE.
YEAH, JOEY HAS THE
BEST BOYFRIEND EVER.
I KISSED KATHY.
MY GOD!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
DOES JOEY KNOW?
NO.
IS THERE ANY WAY--
ANY WAY YOU THINK HE
WILL UNDERSTAND THIS?
YOU OBVIOUSLY
HAVEN'T SCREWED OVER
A LOT OF YOUR FRIENDS.
WHICH WE ALL APPRECIATE.
YOU KNOW, THE SAD THING IS
IF YOU HAD TOLD HIM HOW YOU
FELT BEFORE YOU KISSED HER
KNOWING JOEY, HE PROBABLY
JUST WOULD'VE STEPPED ASIDE.
OH, DON'T SAY THAT.
DON'T SAY THAT.
THAT'S NOT TRUE, IS IT?
YEAH.
HE LOVES YOU.
WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL ME TO DO THAT?!
I DON'T KNOW.
I-I SAID SOMETHING
TO PHOEBE.
THAT'S RIGHT, AND I THOUGHT
IT WAS A REALLY GOOD IDEA.
YEAH, I REMEMBER.
YOU DID.
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
WELL, CHANDLER
YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO TELL HIM.
WHY? WHY DO I HAVE TO TELL HIM?
BECAUSE YOU DO.
YEAH, I KNOW.
HEY.
WOULD IT BE OKAY IF I WROTE
A SONG ABOUT THIS?
HEY.
Wonder Woman:
Steve...?
SAMBUCA MARGARITA?
Are you here?
IS THAT A REAL THING?
WELL, WE ONLY HAD
SAMBUCA, SO IT IS NOW.
LISTEN, UH, JOE, I-I NEED TO--
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING.
WHAT'S UP?
( clearing throat )
IT'S, IT'S ABOUT KATHY.
UM...
UH...
I LIKE HER.
I LIKE HER A LOT, ACTUALLY.
YOU DO?
YEAH.
WELL, YOUR TIMING
COULDN'T BE BETTER
'CAUSE SHE'S NOT MY
GIRLFRIEND ANYMORE.
WHAT?
YEAH, SHE BROKE
UP WITH ME.
OH, UH... WHEN?
JUST NOW,
AFTER ACTING CLASS.
AT FIRST, I THOUGHT SHE WAS
DOING SOME KIND OF SCENE.
THAT'S WHY I LET
PEOPLE WATCH.
OH... MAN, I AM SO SORRY.
ARE YOU, ARE-ARE YOU OKAY?
I'VE BEEN BETTER, YOU
KNOW, BUT I'M ALL RIGHT.
SO, YOU LIKE HER, HUH?
YES, BUT I, I,
I DON'T HAVE TO.
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S, UH...
IT'S OKAY.
YEAH?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHY?
'CAUSE YOU CAME TO ME FIRST.
WELL, I THOUGHT THAT WOULD BE
THE BEST THING TO DO.
BUT, HEY, LISTEN,
JUST SO YOU KNOW--
YOU MIGHT HAVE YOUR
WORK CUT OUT FOR YOU
BECAUSE WHEN I
TALKED TO HER
I KIND OF
GOT THE FEELING
SHE'S INTO SOME
OTHER GUY, SO...
SEE, UH, THAT'S,
THAT'S ACTUALLY
WHAT I WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
I-I THINK I KNOW
WHO THE OTHER GUY IS.
WHO?
IT'S ME.
I'M THE OTHER GUY.
WHAT?
YEAH, I MEAN,
WHEN YOU WERE LATE LAST NIGHT
KATHY AND I GOT TO TALKING
AND...
ONE THING LED TO ANOTHER AND...
AND WHAT?
DID YOU SLEEP WITH HER?
NO! NO, NO, I JUST KISSED HER.
WHAT?! THAT'S EVEN WORSE!
HOW IS THAT WORSE?!
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT IT'S THE SAME!
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I'M
SORRY, BUT THERE WAS
NOTHING I COULD DO.
I THINK I'M IN
LOVE WITH HER.
WHO CARES!
YOU WENT BEHIND MY BACK?!
I'D NEVER DO THAT TO YOU!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I HAVE NO EXCUSES.
I WAS TOTALLY OVER THE LINE.
"OVER THE LINE?"
Y-Y-YOU'RE,
YOU'RE SO FAR PAST THE LINE
THAT YOU CAN'T EVEN SEE
THE LINE!
THE LINE IS A DOT TO YOU.
YES.
YES, RIGHT, AND
I FEEL HORRIBLE.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
OH, MY GOD.
IS THAT WHY
YOU BOUGHT ALL THIS STUFF?!
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WILL NOT WATCH YOUR TV,
I WILL NOT LISTEN TO YOUR STEREO
AND THERE'S A CINNAMON RAISIN
LOAF IN THE NEW BREAD MAKER
THAT I'M NOT GOING TO EAT!
YOU KNOW WHY?
PROBABLY BECAUSE...
BECAUSE IT'S ALL TAINTED
WITH YOUR BETRAYAL.
FROM NOW ON,
THIS APARTMENT IS EMPTY TO ME
AND I'M NOT HAPPY
ABOUT YOU EITHER.
( bread maker ringing )
OH, AND JUST SO YOU KNOW.
I MADE THAT BREAD FOR YOU.
( door slams )
( rooster crows )
( doorbell buzzes )
OH, MY GOD,
HE'S LOST IT.
HE'S TOTALLY LOST IT.
WHAT?
PHOEBE, THIS IS MUSIC
THAT CANNOT GET ANY WORSE.
THERE ARE RATS IN THE BASEMENT
THAT ARE HANGING THEMSELVES.
( explosion )
THANK YOU.
THANKS.
YEAH, I LOST IT.
YOU KNOW, I'M
NOT GOING TO
PLAY ANYMORE.
WOULD YOU...?
CAN YOU FINISH MY SET?
AFTER THAT? YEAH!
NO, I MEAN, IF I CAN HELP.
YEAH.
YEAH, LIKE, I COULD LOSE IT.
WHAT?
I PLAYED BAD ON PURPOSE, GUYS.
OH!
OKAY, SO, YOU WERE
TRYING TO PLAY BAD
THIS WHOLE TIME?
NO, JUST THAT LAST SONG.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]